(UPBEAT MUSIC)
♪ OOH, MY LITTLE PRETTY
ONE, PRETTY ONE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU GONNA GIVE
ME SOME TIME, SHARONA ♪
♪ OOH, YOU MAKE MY MOTOR
RUN, MY MOTOR RUN ♪
♪ GUN IT COMING OFF
OF THE LINE, SHARONA ♪
♪ NEVER GONNA STOP, GIVE
IT UP, SUCH A DIRTY MIND ♪
♪ I ALWAYS GET IT UP FOR THE
TOUCH OF THE YOUNGER KIND ♪
♪ MY, MY, MY, I, I, WHOO ♪
♪ M-M-M-MY SHARONA ♪
♪♪♪
♪ COME A LITTLE CLOSER,
HUH, AH, WILL YA, HUH ♪
♪ CLOSE ENOUGH TO LOOK
IN MY EYES, SHARONA ♪
♪ KEEPING IT A
MYSTERY GETS TO ME ♪
♪ RUNNING DOWN THE LENGTH
OF MY THIGHS, SHARONA ♪
♪ NEVER GONNA STOP, GIVE
IT UP, SUCH A DIRTY MIND ♪
♪ I ALWAYS GET IT UP FOR THE
TOUCH OF THE YOUNGER KIND ♪
♪ MY, MY, MY, I, I, WHOO ♪
♪ M-M-M-MY SHARONA ♪
♪ YO ♪
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
♪ WHEN YOU GONNA GIVE
TO ME, G-GIVE TO ME ♪
♪ IS IT JUST A MATTER
OF TIME, SHARONA ♪
♪ IS IT D-D-DESTINY, D-DESTINY ♪
♪ OR IS IT JUST A GAME
IN MY MIND, SHARONA ♪
♪ NEVER GONNA STOP, GIVE
IT UP, SUCH A DIRTY MIND ♪
♪ I ALWAYS GET IT UP FOR THE
TOUCH OF THE YOUNGER KIND ♪
♪ MY, MY, MY, I, I, WHOO ♪
♪ M-M-M-MY, MY, MY, I, I, WHOO ♪
♪ M-M-M-MY SHARONA ♪
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
♪ OH, MY SHARONA ♪